Guide to the Samuel R. Delany Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 2017 acquisition, 200.17; (249 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Materials deposited in 2015 and 2016, 1942-2016; 41.42; (41 boxes)
    - Manuscripts, 1966-2016
      - Fragments by SRD, 1966-2015
        - "Always Coming Home", undated (Box 143)
          Contains: "Always Coming Home", 2 fragments. Also includes: "The American Shore"; "Atlantis Revisited"; "Beatitudes"; "Coming Out"; 'Dark Reflections'; "Dichtung Und Science Fiction", 2 fragments; "Forward to an Aterword", 2 fragments.
        - "Heinlein", 1976-1985, undated (Box 143)
          Contains: "Heinlein" (undated). Also includes: "Mike, Jesus, and Me" (undated); "New York, Winter" (1985); "New Years Letter" (undated); "Neither the First Word nor the Last on Structuralism, Post Structuralism, Semiotics or Deconstruction for SF Readers" (undated); "Sturgeon" (1976).
        - "Politics/Paraliterature", 1966-1976, undated (Box 143)
          Contains: "Politics/Paraliterature" (undated). Also includes: "Preface" (1966-1976); "Presentation on the Self in Everyday Life" (undated); "The Ruins of the Towers", 4 fragments (undated); "Russ" (undated); "Science Fiction and Literature -- Or the Conscience of the King" (undated).
        - "Some Presumptuous Approaches to Science Fiction", 1989-2001, undated (Box 143)
          Contains: "Some Presumptuous Approaches to Science Fiction" (undated). Also includes: "Some Reflections on The Fall of the Towers" (undated); "Some Reflections Toward a Reading of Dhalgren" (undated); "Stay Back and Die" (2001); "To Read the Dispossessed" (undated); "Variables in Gay Slang / Constants in Gay Oppression" (undated); "Twilight in the Rue Morgue" (1989).
        - Untitled fragments, undated; (2 folders) (Box 143)
          Contains: untitled fragments, 35 fragments.
        - 'Tales of Neveryon' by K. Leslie Steiner (pseudonym), undated (Box 143)
          Contains: 'Tales of Neveryon' by K. Leslie Steiner (pseudonym for SRD).
        - Speeches, 1986 April 15, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: speeches. Includes: "Introduction to the Reading by Barbara Wise and Samuel R. Delany of the 'Tale of Plagues and Carnivals'" (1986 April 15); "Lecture Topics" (undated); "Reading at work, and other activities frowned-on by Authority: A reading of Donna Haraway's 'Manifesto for Cyborgs'", 2 copies (undated); "Theodore Sturgeon (1918-1985)" (undated).
        - Interviews with SRD, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: interviews with SRD, 7 fragments.
        - Fragments by others, 1995-2010, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: fragments by others. Includes: 'Algorithm' by Jean Mark Gawron (undated); "Bipartite: Refractions of 'Empire'" by Dennis O'Neal (undated); "Bye, Bye, Love" by Frank Romeo (undated); "Night, Death, Love" and "Down from the Lake (Hennepin Ave.)" by Riawa Smith (1995); "Exits" by Matthew Barbehenn (2010); "On Science Fiction as Political Discourse, or The Revolutionary Significance of Buck Rogers" by Gregory Renault (undated); "Snowbrother" by S. M. Stirling (undated); untitled, 8 fragments (undated).
        - Unidentified fragments, undated (Box 144)
      - Corrections, 1978-2016
        - Relating to biography of SRD, 1978-2004, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: [corrections] relating to biography of SRD (undated). Also includes: [corrections] relating to 'Bread and Wine'; relating to 'Dark Reflections' (undated); "Corrections for the Vintage Edition of 'Dhalgren'" (2001 August 23); relating to 'Dhalgren' (undated); "Corrections to be Made in 'Dhalgren'" (1985); "Errata Sheet for 'The Jewel-Hinged Jaw'" (1978); "Correction List (Partial) for 'The Mad Man', Voyant Edition" (2004); "Additions, restored cuts, and corrections for the Plume trade paperback editions of 'The Motion of Light in Water'" (undated).
        - Relating to 'Neveryon' series, 1983-1986, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: [corrections] relating to 'Neveryon' series, 12 sets of corrections (1983-1986). Also includes: "Notes" foe 'Dhalgren' (undated).
        - Relating to 'Phallos!', 1995-2016, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: [corrections] relating to 'Phallos!' (undated). Also includes: "To Read 'The Dispossessed'" (undated); "Corrections for 'Silent Interviews'" (1995); "Last Minute Notes on 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders'" (undated); relating to 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders' (undated); "Corrections for Works (1998 March); untitled, 2 fragments (2016 January 22, undated).
      - Notes, undated
        - Re: "Identity Shopping" paper, undated (Box 144)
          Contains: [notes] re: "Identity Shopping" paper. Also includes: "KENlist", re: family of SRD; re: logic and knowledge; re: Sade and Samuel Richardson; re: Nietzsche on language; holograph notes.
      - Manuscripts by others, undated
        - Files, undated; (11 folders) (Box 144)
          Contains: files. Includes: "The Walls of Uruk", screenplay synopsis by Bernard K. Kay, typescript and hologrpah, includes printed materials, notebooks, correspondence, subfile re: clippings of Sumer/Uruk (folders 9-10); "Omitted Pages from the 'Steiner Introduction' by K. Leslie Steiner (folder 11); "Some Remarks Toward a Reading of Dhalgren" by K. Leslie Steiner (folder 11); "Samuel R. Delany" by K. Leslie Steiner (folder 11); "Samuel R. Delany Introduction" by Connie Willis (folder 11); 'The Walls of Uruk' by Bernard K. Kay (folders 12-19).
        - Files, undated; (5 folders) (Box 145)
          Contains: files. Includes: 'The Walls of Uruk' by Bernard K. Kay.
    - Correspondence, 1947-2016
      - Files, undated
        Includes: autograph letters; typed letters; autograph notes; typed notes. May include: printed material; professsional materials; photographs; manuscripts; financial materials.
        - "A" - "D", undated (Box 145)
        - "E" - "J", undated (Box 146)
        - "J" - "R", undated (Box 147)
        - "R" - "Z", untitled, undated (Box 148)
          Includes notable: Russ, Joanna.
      - General, 1947-2016
        Includes: autograph letters; typed letters; autograph notes; typed notes. May include: printed material; professional materials; photographs; manuscripts; financial materials.
        - General correspondence, 1947-1969 (Box 149)
          Includes notable: Caruso, Paul.
        - General correspondence, 1970-1979; (5 folders) (Box 149)
        - General correspondence, 1980-1989; (12 folders) (Box 149)
          Includes notables: Gates, Henry Louis; Russ, Joanna.
        - General correspondence, 1990-1994; (2 folders) (Box 149)
        - General correspondence, 1995-1999; (6 folders) (Box 150)
        - General correspondence, 2000-2010; (13 folders) (Box 150)
          Includes notables: Copjec, Joan; Diaz, Junot.
        - General correspondence, 2011-2016; (18 folders) (Box 151)
          Includes notables: Diaz, Junot; Ellison, Harlan; Lethem, Jonathan.
        - General correspondence, 2016; (2 folders) (Box 152)
          Includes notable: Diaz, Junot.
        - General correspondence, undated; (4 folders) (Box 152)
          Includes notables: Diaz, Junot; Russ, Joanna.
        - Paul Caruso correspondence, undated (Box 152)
          Contains: correspondence with Paul Caruso.
    - Printed materials, 1944-2015
      - Files, undated
        May include: correspondence; manuscripts; professional materials.
        - "A" - "C", undated (Box 152)
        - "D" - "S", undated (Box 153)
        - "S" - "Z", untitled, undated (Box 154)
      - Articles, undated
        - Journal articles, 1964-2015, undated; (12 folders) (Box 155)
          Contains: journal articles by SRD, 1973-2012, undated (folders 1-4); journal articles by others, 1964-2015, undated (folders 5-12).
      - Internet printouts, 2004-2015, undated; (3 folders) (Box 155)
      - Journals, 1967-2014, undated; (5 folders) (Box 155)
      - Booklets, 1944-2011; (2 folders) (Box 156)
      - Newsletters, 1959-2009; (2 folders) (Box 156)
      - Catalogues, 1991-2015 (Box 156)
      - Comic books: "Strange Attractors" #1-8, undated (Box 156)
      - Business cards, membership cards, subscription forms, postcards, book covers, undated (Box 156)
      - Magazines, 1962-2012 (Box 157)
      - Magazines, 1962-2012 (Box 158)
      - Magazines, 1962-2012; (5 folders) (Box 156)
      - Magazine clippings, 1985-2011, undated (Box 156)
      - Programs, 1969-2015 (Box 156)
      - Calendar, 2007 (Box 158)
      - Pamphlets and fliers, 1960-2015, undated (Box 156)
        Contains: pamphlets (1960-2015, undated); fliers (1982-2011, undated).
      - Newspapers, 1960-2005 (Box 159)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1959-2014, undated; (3 folders) (Box 159)
      - Proofs, 1957-2014
        - 'The Tale of Plagues and Carnivals', undated; (2 folders) (Box 160)
        - 'The American Shore', 2014 (Box 160)
        - 'Atlantis', 2009, undated (Box 160)
          Contains: 'Atlantis' (2009). Also includes: 'Bread and Wine', afterword (undated); 'The Mad Man' (undated); "The Motion of Light" (undated); 'Phallos' (undated).
        - 'Bread and Wine', 1994-1999 (Box 160)
          Contains: 'Bread and Wine' (1999). Also includes: 'Equinox' (1994).
        - 'The Mirror and the Maze', 1957-1969 (Box 160)
        - 'The Mirror and the Maze', 1957-1969; (2 folders) (Box 161)
        - 'The Mad Man', 1995; (3 folders) (Box 162)
        - 'Queerly Classed', 1996 (Box 163)
        - "From Phallos", 2003 (Box 163)
        - 'Shorter Views', undated (Box 163)
        - 'Starboard Wine', 1984, undated (Box 163)
          Contains: 'Starboard Wine' (1984). Also includes: "Times Square Red" (undated).
    - Professional files, 1976-2016
      - Files, 1992-2008
        May include: printed material; manuscripts; correspondence; financial materials.
        - "A" - "E", undated (Box 163)
        - "E" - "U", 1992-2008 (Box 164)
          Includes: file relating to Susan Sontag.
        - Untitled, undated; (9 folders) (Box 165)
      - Biography of SRD, conference materials, curricula vitae, 1986-2015, undated (Box 165)
        Contains: biography of SRD (undated); conference materials (1986-2015); curricula vitae, SRD and others (undated).
      - Address lists, course materials, 1995-2011, undated (Box 165)
        Contains: address lists (1995-1999); course materials (1995-2011, undated).
      - Facebook posts, 2007-2014 (Box 165)
      - Interviews, 1976-2015, undated; (2 folders) (Box 165)
      - Interviews, 1976-2015, undated; (7 folders) (Box 166)
      - Letters of recommendation, memos, reports, 1986-2014, undated (Box 166)
        Contains: letters of recommendation (1986-2014); memos (1995-2007, undated); reports (1991).
      - Reviews of SRD, schedules and itineraries, 1984-2016, undated (Box 166)
        Contains: reviews of SRD (2002-2009, undated); schedules and itineraries (1984-2016).
      - Business cards, train tickets, contact book entries, undated (Box 173)
    - Photographs, 1942-2016
      - Files, undated
        - Personal, undated; (22 folders) (Box 166)
          Includes: "A" - "Z", untitled.
        - Personal, undated; (2 folders) (Box 167)
          Includes: untitled.
        - Personal, undated (Box 168)
        - Personal, undated; (3 folders) (Box 169)
          Includes: untitled (folders 3-5).
      - General, 1942-2016
        - Personal, 1944-1996, undated; (4 folders) (Box 169)
          Contains: personal photographs. Includes: untitled relating to flight to Panama City, Florida and Thanksgiving get-together, photoprints and negatives, 1995 November (folder 4); untitled relating to headshots of SRD and Vince Czyz, 3 photoprints, undated (folder 4); untitled relating to old family photos from formal events, 4 photoprints, undated (folder 4); untitled relating to unidentified friends and SRD NYC apartment, photoprints and negatives, circa 1990 (folder 4); untitled relating to classroom lecture, negatives, undated (folder 5); untitled relating to family/friends' house, photoprints and negatives, 1996 (folder 5); untitled relating to home of Dennis and SRD, photoprints and negatives, 1996 January 3 (folder 5); untitled relating to family photos, photoprints, 1944-1945, undated (folder 5); abstract art images, photoprint and clipping, undated (folder 6); friends, 42 photoprints, 1996, undated (folder 7).
        - Personal, 1942-2016, undated; (9 folders) (Box 170)
          Contains: personal photographs. Includes: family, 2016, undated (folders 8-11); Iva Hacker-Delany, photoprints and paper printouts, 1977, undated (folder 12); photos of SRD and family, 32 photoprints, 1942-1970s (folder 13); SRD "mini-dig" computer for Bronx High School science fair, 2 photoprints, undated (folder 14); photos of SRD and Marilyn Hacker, 9 photoprints, undated (folder 15); photos of SRD, Marilyn Hacker, and friends, 11 photoprints, undated (folder 16).
        - Personal, undated (Box 171)
          Contains: personal photographs.
        - Professional, 1966-2006, undated; (2 folders) (Box 169)
          Contains: professional photographs. Includes: headshots, photoprints and paper printouts, 1966, undated (folder 1); photos of readings and awards, photoprint, paper printouts, printout with holograph note from Larry McCaffrey, 1976-2006, undated (folder 2).
        - Professional, circa 1976 (Box 170)
          Contains: professional photographs. Includes: "Star Wars" set photos, 10 photoprints, circa 1976 (folder 17).
        - Files: re: 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue', undated (Box 171)
          Contains: photographs re: 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue'.
      - Negatives, undated
        - Files: "Martin Turkivensky taken by B. Kay, Date?", undated
          Contains: approximately 40 negatives.
        - General, undated (Box 170)
          Contains: approximately 20 negative strips, 1 slide.
      - Albums, 1942
        - "Our Baby", baby photos of SRD, 1942 (Box 172)
        - Christmas photos, undated (Box 172)
        - New York City, SRD apartment, SRD and friends, undated; (2 folders) (Box 172)
          Contains: 2 photo albums.
  - Materials not processed on deposit, 1940-2017; 39.67; (70 boxes)
    Some of these materials were briefly held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University, circa 2016. Others were received by the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript directly from Samuel R. Delany.
    - Notebooks and correspondence, 2004-03-2015-01 (Box 175)
    - Notebooks and correspondence, 2006-2007-01 (Box 176)
    - Notebooks and correspondence, 2004-2016 (Box 177)
    - Bound typescript drafts: 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', 2010-2011 (Box 178)
    - Typescript drafts: 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', 2010 (Box 179)
    - Printed materials; Callaloo journal issues; course packets, circa 1996-2015 (Box 180)
    - Typescript drafts by SRD; bound 'Dhalgren' movie script by Eric A. Zimmerman; photocopied material, circa 1981-2006 (Box 181)
    - Typescript draft: unidentified work of fiction, undated (Box 182)
    - Posters for symposium, 2006-03- (Box 183)
    - Typescript drafts by SRD and others; legal contract; postcard; photocopy of comic, circa 1978-2010 (Box 184)
    - Obituary for Joanna Russ; typescript draft by Russ: 'Putting It All Together: Conversations Among Feminists', 2011, undated (Box 185)
    - Legal and financial documents, 1942 - circa 2015 (Box 186)
    - Typescript works by SRD and others, related documents, circa 1980s - 2015 (Box 187)
    - Typescript drafts by SRD and other; letters and typescript drafts from Richard Kostelanetz; correspondence; corrections and inserts; holograph notes, circa 1970s - 2010s (Box 188)
    - Typescript drafts, including 'About Writing', 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', essays and essay fragments, circa 1981 - 2011 (Box 189)
    - Notebooks, 2015 (Box 190)
    - Notebooks, 2004-11-2005-03 (Box 191)
    - 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', bound typescript drafts and setting copies, 2010-2011 (Box 192)
    - 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', bound typescript drafts and setting copies, circa 2010 (Box 193)
    - Works and drafts by others, typescript and holograph; photocopied printed works by others; correspondence; professional papers, 1983-2015 (Box 194)
    - Professional materials, including student work; works and drafts by others, typescript and photocopy; letters to SRD; printed work; holograph notes, 1977-2010 (Box 195)
    - Work by others, typescript, photocopy, and printed; holograph notes; correspondence; student work; typescript, photocopied, and printed work by others, holograph notes, correspondence, circa 1980s - 2015 (Box 196)
    - Work by others, typescript, photocopy; internet printouts, 2000-2010 (Box 197)
    - Typescript drafts by others; letters to SRD, 1979-1997, undated (Box 198)
    - Works, drafts, and fragments by others, typescript; letters; medical receipt, circa 1980s - 2000s (Box 199)
    - Work and drafts by others, typescript, photocopy, and printout; flyers for movie screening; SRD translation of "The Drunken Ship" by Arthur Rimbaud, 1960 - 2010s (Box 200)
    - Financial and legal materials; works by others, typescript, proofs; photocopies of printed work by SRD and others; 'Hogg' proof, 1970s - 2010s (Box 201)
    - Work by others, typescript and photocopy; photocopied printed work by SRD; collected material re: "Khatru Symposium: Women in SF", typescript draft and printed version; letters and notes to SRD and family; financial material; legal material; medical material; Iva Hacker-Delany: schoolwork, related documents, 1973-2011 (Box 202)
    - 'Dhalgren' screenplay concept art; financial material; legal material; travel documents; application by Marilyn Hacker; graduate school application by other; letters and notes to SRD, 1970s - 2015 (Box 203)
    - Notebooks and correspondence, 2011-2013, undated (Box 204)
    - Notebooks and correspondence, 2007-2011 (Box 205)
    - Notebooks; Iva Hacker-Delany schoolwork, 1982-2009 (Box 206)
    - Notebooks; email correspondence; program, 1989-2009 (Box 207)
    - Material by and relating to Mia Wolff; annotated printed works by SRD; photoprint, 1988-2015 (Box 208)
      - "SF-Eye Interview Takayuki for Brown", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Iva's Disk", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "mBasic/oBasic Double Pass", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Perfect Writer Edit - Working", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Perfect Writer", 2 copies, undated; 2 (Box 245)
      - "Atlantis", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Bob / June 87", 1987-06; 1 (Box 245)
      - "J/F/R/D (Frags): Disk One: A-B-C", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Revised Ruins / Foundaleom: Bad Sec - 35: Disk Two: e-f", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Ruins / Found: Why We Got Married: 'c'", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Bob, Kathy, Mog, et al: May", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Nov 1985: Bob, Mog, McC: Omet", 2 copies, 1985-11; 2 (Box 245)
      - "Bob 2. mss: May 86", 1986-05; 1 (Box 245)
      - "More Bob (May-June 86)", 1986-05-1986-06; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Steiner / BB", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Letters / Late Jan 1987 (Pho)", 1 (Box 245)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Iva Hacker", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Bob, Jan 1987", 1987-01; 1 (Box 245)
      - "The Ruins of the Towers", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "The Ruins of the Towers: Back-Up", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Ruins of the Towers: Disk 2", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Ruins of the Towers: Disk 2: (Back-Up)", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Messina - September", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Propositions", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Neveryon Apparatus (Insert on T. of G.)", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Neveryon Apparatus", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "April '87: Kan James / Othelo", 1987-04; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Autobiography: One & two", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "MBasic", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Feb 88 - and back letters and stuff (On the Unspeakable)", 1988-02; 1 (Box 245)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Camera Obscura", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "McCaffry / Gregory: Printed Version", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "McCaffry / Gregory: Printed Version: Back-Up", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "McCaffery / Gregory: Disk 2: Printed Version", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "McCaffery / Gregory: Disk 2: (Back-Up): Printed Version", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "McCaffrey / Gregory Interview - Aug 25, 83: Back-Up: A, B, C", 1983-08; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Interview Disk #2: D E Notes letter: Back-up #1", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Wagner/Artuad: W/A mss/Pin: back-up", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Tatsumi Interview", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Takayuki Tatsumi Interview: Disk 2", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Tatsumi Interview: Back-Up", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Refractions of Empire: Empire Interview - 1", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Empire Interview - 2", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Revised Interview: Disk #2: Semiology of Silence", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Revised Interview: Disk #1: Semiology of Silence", undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - Audio recording: "Time Considered as a Helix of Semi-Precious Stones" by Marc Satterwhite, performed by The Verdehr Trio, undated; 1 (Box 245)
      - Video recording: "Queer Thoughts and the Politics of Sex", SRD lecture at Dartmouth, 2005-10-31; 1 (Box 245)
      - "Forward, Red Banners Flying High - Revolutionary Songs", undated; 1 (Box 246 (Record album storage))
    - Papers relating to young SRD; papers by and relating to Margaret Delany, including notebook; Iva's tooth; name tags; certificates; travel documents, 1940-2016 (Box 209)
    - 1989 Hugo Awards Winners picture/collage with holograph note (Box 210)
    - Materials by and relating to Iva Hacker-Delany; school report for SRD; financial materials; memorabilia, 1947-1990s (Box 211)
    - Materials by and relating to Iva Hacker-Delany; certificate for Margaret Delany; miniature booklet; art by Jim Cogswell with note; item removal request, 1970s-2015 (Box 212)
    - Certificate for Margaret Delany, 1980-1981 (Box 213)
    - 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', bound and unbound typescript drafts, circa 2010-2012 (Box 214)
    - 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', bound typescript drafts, circa 2010-2012 (Box 215)
    - Journal entries, typescript; Facebook post printout; notebook excerpts; medical documents; correspondence; documents relating to Joseph Cox, 1957-2016 (Box 216)
    - Corrections and writings, printout and photocopy; material relating to "Bellona" by Jay Scheib; printed journal issues, magazine, pamphlet; research file regarding Mary Kelly; 'Attack Queers' by Richard Goldstein, proof; financial documents, 1969-2016 (Box 217)
    - "Good Times" periodical, 2016-03 (Box 218)
    - 'Through the Valley of the Nest of Spiders', bound typescript draft; course packets; printed books by others; photocopied work by others, circa 1950s-2010s (Box 219)
    - Printed periodicals; 'Hogg' corrections; typescript drafts and fragments by SRD and others; professional documents; printout essay by other, circa 2000s (Box 220)
    - Work by others, printout, photocopied, typescript, proofs; 'A, B, C, Three Early Science Fiction Novels', bound typescript draft with holograph corrections; photoprint; "Driftnotes", bound typescript/printout; bound Wikipedia printouts relating to SRD; 'Phallos', bound photocopies with corrections; bound printouts relating to philosophy; 'The Motion of Light in Water', bound proof; 'Phallos', typescript draft; "The Owls", bound typescript drafts; 'Dhalgren' screenplay by Eric Zimmerman, bound draft; introduction for Junot Diaz, typescript, 1980s-2010s (Box 221)
    - Professional materials; bound Wikipedia printouts with works by and relating to SRD; essay regarding SRD; Encyclopedia Britannica entry on SRD, circa 2000s (Box 222)